Guide to the Center for Jewish Living records, 1985-2015.
Center for Jewish Living records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Center for Jewish Living records, 1985-2015.
37-3-3431
Turkish, Norman A.
1.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, newspapers, publications, printed materials, memorabilia.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, clippings, brochures, broadsides, and other records relating to the founding of the Center for Jewish Living and events associated with the Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, clippings, brochures, broadsides, and other records relating to the founding of the Center for Jewish Living and events associated with the Center. Included are books and items relating to art exhibits; broadsides relating to events; poster and cookbook by Denise Phillips; items relating to Masters in Excellence events in 1998 and 2005 including tape recordings, posters, publicity materials, invitations, and souvenirs; items relating to a "Cantorial Weekend," 2011 including a CD of photographs by Cheryl D. Sinkow. Alphabetic subject files of material relating to individuals who had involvement with the Center or participated in events.
Materials for the inaugural "Harold I. Saperstein '31 Cornell Student Topical Sermon Contest" in 2011, honoring Rabbi Harold Saperstein, include publicity materials, invitation, program, and menu. Also, remarks from the judges (Todd Olson, Howard Erlich, and Rhoda Possen) by Todd Olson, talk on Harold I. Saperstein by Elaine D. Engst, DVD of sermon by John Ertl, and CD of photographs by Cheryl D. Sinkow. Posters and other items for the 2012 Saperstein contest, honoring Milton Konvitz, including the winning sermon by Sarah Grace Victor. Programs, menu, and souvenir booklet for the 2013 contest, honoring Sol Linowitz; also includes framed copy of photographs taken at the signing of the Panama Canal Treaties on Sept. 7, 1977 from the collection of the Organization of American States. Invitation, programs, and menu from the 2014 Saperstein contest, honoring Raymond Reisler '27, a DVD of the Gala Dinner, and sermon videos from the contest.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Turkish, Norman A.,; Canaday, Sara Beth,; Chamorro, Koldo.; Engst, Elaine D.; Ertl, John.; Konvitz, Milton R. (Milton Ridvas), 1908-2003.; Konvitz, Milton R. (Milton Ridvas), 1908-2003; Linowitz, Sol M., 1913-2005.; Linowitz, Sol M., 1913-2005; Olson, Todd.; Phillips, Denise.; Reisler, Raymond; Reisler, Raymond.; Saperstein, Harold I.; Saperstein, Harold I.; Singer, Alex.; Sinkow, Cheryl D.; Victor, Sarah Grace.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University; Cornell University. Center for Jewish Living.; Organization of American States; Organization of American States.
Subjects:
Jewish college students -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.; Jewish college students; Students
Places:
New York (State) -- Ithaca
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Masters in Excellence material including floppy disk and articles, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Articles regarding Rabbi Saperstein as Ambassador for International Religious Freedom, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Articles, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Flyers and broadsides of events (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Jewish Cooking, signed by Denies Phillips, 2001 (Box 1)
- Jewish Roots In Spain, 1988 (Box 1)
- Flyers, clippings, misc., 1985-2009 (Box 2, Folder 1-12)
- Jewish High Holy Days at Cornell, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Frank Robinson Dinner and Cantorial Weekend; Saperstein Sermon Contest, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  -includes two CDs of photographs by Cheryl D. Sinkow (CD-1048-1049) and one DVD of the sermon (DVD-709)
- CUL Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- First Jewish Outreach/Greek Night Dinner - song book, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Center for Jewish Living - Constitution, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Fundraising, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Peter Lipman - Wulf Art Exhibit, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Alex Singer Art Exhibit, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Von Babelsberg nach Hollywood, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Items from Center for Jewish Living scrapbook, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Misc. flyers and programs, 1990's-2000's (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
- Project to improve Jewish life at Cornell, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Distinguished Scholars' Sabbath - program, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Topical Sermon Contest winners, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Saperstein sermon contest memorabilia, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Saperstein sermon contest memorabilia, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Saperstein sermon contest memorabilia, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  -contains DVD of gala dinner (DVD-1195)
- Masters in Excellence material, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Saperstein sermon contest memorabilia, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Donor wall dedication, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Masters in Excellence silver-plated wine goblet, 2005; MU-2001 (Box 3)
- Masters in Excellence wallet, 2005; MU-2130 (Box 3)
- Photo of signing of the Panama Canal Treaties and celebration, images include Ambassador Sol M. Linowitz, 1977 (Box 4)
- "Preserving the Constitution in the Next Millenium", tape cassettes (contains duplicates), 1998; tr-9129-9135, 9318 (Box 4)
- Alpha Subject Files
  - A and B awards, 2005-2012 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Abbe, Cyrus, 1990, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Abelson, Joshua, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Abraham, Johnathan and Nicole Clem, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Abrams, David, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Abrams, Floyd (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ackman, Aaron J., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Acquarella, William, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Adamit, Aminadov and Sarah Lyn, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Adelman, Kenneth, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ades, Joseph, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Adler, Daniel, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Adler, Hon. Stephen J., 2012-2015 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Aharonovitch, David, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Aharoni, Ido, 2005-2014 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Ahitow, Andrew, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Aizenberg, Rabbi, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Akiba Hebrew Academy, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Shannon Albanese Interiors, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Alexander, Bernard, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Alexander, Renee T., 2015 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Allied Old English, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Alpha Chi Omega, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Altman, Ezra, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Altschuler, Glenn, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Aminoff, Melvin, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Amundsen, Minakshi, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Aneselovits, Elisha, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Anderson, Richard, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Rabbi Marc D. Angel, 2005-2009 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Angell, Marissa, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Angelo's, 2007, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Ansel, Bernard, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Ariel, David- Oxford University, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Arking, Al, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Aronson, Robert L., 2012 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Arthur, CJ, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Ashkol Wine Co. Inc, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Aswad and Ingraham, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Auburn Party Rental Center, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Avnet Inc., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - A and Y Sofrei Stam, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Bakstansky, Peter, 1989-1990, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Babelsberg to Hollywood Art Exhibit, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Leo Baeck Institute, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Lauren Bailyn, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Baker, Beverly, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Ankur Bajaj, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Balamut, Stephen (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Balsam, Philip and Rhonda, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Bando, Patricia, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Barney, Grossman, Roth and Dubow, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Barcelo, John J, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Barker, Robert, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Baris, Paul H., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Rog Baron (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Barrett, Monica C., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Barrow, Karen, 2007, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Barton's Bonbonniere, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Basterra, Josue, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Baum, Claire (Jessica), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Baum Egg Farms, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Baum, Linda: Bat mitzvah for Jennifer, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Baum, Rebecca (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Beck, Jacob and Ruth, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Begley, Brian J, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Beim, Martin, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Bell, June D, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Bellin, Judah, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Benamy, Lonny (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Bender, Stephen, 2012-2014 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Benefield, Jerry L, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Ben-Gurion, David (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Bennett, Laura A, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Berg, Fred J, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Bergman, Joel, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Berggren, Kathy, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Berkowitz, Jeffrey E, 2005, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Berkowitz, Yael, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Berle, Milton, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Berlin, Richard, III, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Berman, Earl, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Berman, Gur, 1991, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Berman, Roger (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Berman, Reuben, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Bermant, Alison K, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Bernhardy, Herbert, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Bernstein, Charles L, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Bernstein, Daniel, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Bernstein, Marver, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Bernstein-on-Essex St. (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Bernstein, Robert, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Bernstein, Vera L, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Bernstein, William, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Best Western, 2005, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Bestress Mattress, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Beth Medrash Goroha, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Bethe, Hans A (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Beuret, Robert R, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Black, Barry C, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Black, Bob, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Blackman, Harry A, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Bielsker, Diane, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Billaur, Barbara, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Bilson, Malcolm (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Biondo, Catherine, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Blaich, Efrat, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Blau, Rivkah (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Blitzer, Wolf, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Blume, Larry and Marilyn Edid, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Blumenthal, Stephen (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Blumin, Deborah (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Bodman Foundation, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Boesky, Seema, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Bogomilsky, Rabbi, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Bolen, Patricia, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Bolton, John, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Bond, Alan, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Boor, Kathryn J, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Bores, Alex, 2012-2015 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Borgenicht, Grace, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Borkowf, Craig, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Bornstein, David, 1991, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Bornstein, Richard, 1990-2015 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Bornstein, Susan P, 2008, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Bosworth, Phyllis, 2005-2006, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Boslett, Terri, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Boston Eruv (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Boston University (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Botwinick-Wolfensohn Foundation, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Bouchey, Rodney Peter (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Box and Moore Storage, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Boxer, Barbara, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Boxer, Tim and David, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Brainson, David, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Brann, Ross, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Brazin, Lawrence, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Brody, Martin, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Bronfman, Edgar M, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Brothers, Dr. Joyce, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Brown Cow Farm, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Brown Hillel, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Brown's Meats, Buffalo, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Brown, Meredith, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Brown, Richard, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Brown, Sarah, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Bruckheimer, Robert, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Brueggemann, Alison, 2013-2015 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Bruner Foundation, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - BT Glass, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Buck Environmental Labs, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - The Buffalo Jewish Review (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Buckiet, Etan, 2011, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Bumble Bee Seafoods, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Burch, Norah, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Burness, John F, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Burruss Transfer Inc., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Bursky, Jennifer, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Burstein, Blance, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Bush, Larry, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Bush/Quayle, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - President Buch speech on 350 yrs in US (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Business Services Unltd., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Buttenwieser, Lawrence, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Cadett Marketing Inc. (bracelets), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Cahn, Edmond (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Calf Audio, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Call, David L, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Callnin, Bill J, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Campbell, William E. Jr. (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Campus Travel Service, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Candy Land, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Canlis, Brian (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Cantarovici, Sergio F (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Cappell, Marcie, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Carl, Donald Ray, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Carmichael, Calum M, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Carpenter Northeast Industries, Inc, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Carpet Bazaar, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Carter, Lael, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Casarett, Alison P, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Cascadilla Tree Care, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Cayne, James, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Cayuga Landscape, 1989-2010 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Cayuga Landscape (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Cayuga Lumber, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cayuga Press, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cayuga Signs, 1989, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Center Capital Corp., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Center for Holocaust studies, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Challenge Industries, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Allan Chambliss Architect, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Chase Lincoln First Bank, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Chideckel, Mollie, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chirel, Victor J, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chock, Carol I, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chuck's Cleaning Co., 2005 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ciao Bella, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ciaschi, Dietershagen, Little and Mickelson, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Citizens Savings Bank, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - City of Ithaca Building Department, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - City of Ithaca Fire Department, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - City of Ithaca Youth Empowerment Service, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - City of Ithaca Water and Sewer, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CJL Donor Wall, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CJL Endowment Board of Directors, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CJL Commencement, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CJL Insurance, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - CJL Insurance, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - CJL/KDH Closing (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CJL Insurance, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CJL-LR Oriental Rugs (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CJL Room Leases, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - CJL Senior Party, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Chicago Hardware Foundry Div. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Clapp Car Service, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Rev. Dr. Clarke, Kenneth I, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Clarke Vantage Line (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Cleaning Authority, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Cleveland Jewish News, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Clooney, George, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - C and M Enterprises Co., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Coated Sales, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Coates, Diane M (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Elmira Coca Cola, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Cohen, Ada S, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Cohen, Alan, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Cohen, Avis and Marshall (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Cohen, Brett, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Cohen, David, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Cohen, Jeffrey M, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Cohen, William H, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Cohen, Zipporah (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Colbert, Loren, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Collegetown Motor Lodge, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Collins, Lance R, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Collins and Walton, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - C and M Lock Security, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Colonial Cleaners, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Colony House Foods, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Colucci, Liz, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Conable, Barber B, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Conrad Rice Mill, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Consolidated Tea Company, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Contadina Foods Inc., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Cooke, J Robert, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Cornell Review, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Cooper, Warren, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Cornell, Ezra, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Court, Emma, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Craft, Hal, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Crane, Melissa, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Creative Types, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Cronin, Peter (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Cronin, Tara, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Crow, Violeta J (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Crown Trophy, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - CU 104 West!, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - CU Catering, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - CU Campus Store, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - CU Chronicle, 1991-2012 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - CU Class of '56, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - CU Cinema, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - CU Commencement, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - CU Commencement, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - CU Conference Services, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - CU Diary, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - CU EAS, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - CU Einaudi Center, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - CU Eruv Map, 2011-2015 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - CU Forensics Soc., 2012 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - CU Grounds Department, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - CU Ground Lease, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - CU History Department, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - CU Homecoming, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - CU House Manager, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - CU Humanities Events Calendar, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - CU Institute for African Development, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - CU Johnson Museum, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - CU Koster Facilities Report, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - CU Latin American Studies, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - CU Law School, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - CU Life Safety Services, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - CU Magazine Alumni News, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - CU Memorandum, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - CU National Resources Department, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - CU Plantations, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - CU Photography, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - CU Physical Sciences Building, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - CU Police, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - CU Publication Services, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - CU Real Estate, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - CU Reunion, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - CU ROTC, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - CU-SFC, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - CU Signs, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - CU Surrender of ground lease, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - CU Tower Club, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - CU Department of Theater (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - CU Transportation, 1988-2012 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - CU Telecommunications, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - CU United Religious Works, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Cuomo, Governor Mario, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Curtiss, Pete, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Cypress, Rebecca, 2002-2012 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Daghita, Kathleen G, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Daitchman, Murray, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Dalton's American Decorative Arts (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Damiani, Laura, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Dartmouth College, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - D'Amato, Sen. Alfonse, 1988-1989, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Data flow, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Data search, Susan Feldman, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Dawn, Adam, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Daven, James, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Davidovitz, Andrew, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Davis, Elliott, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Davis, George A, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Davis, Harvey D, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Davis, Johnathan L, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Davis, Morton J, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Dawidowicz, Lucy S, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Dayan, Nimrod, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Dayan, Yael (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Delgado, Gilbert, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Denton, Keyser, LaBrecque, and Moore, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Dermer, Irving, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Dettelbach, Cynthia, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Devoogd, Tim, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Aaron Diamond Foundation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Diamond Crystal Salt Co., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Diamond, Jeff, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Dicker, Karl (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Dickman, Reni, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Ciaschi, Dietershagen, Little and Mickelson, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Dillon, John, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Dine, Elliot, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Direct Page, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Dobrow, Diane, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - De Domenico, Ellen, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Donohue- Halverson, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - D'Oro, Stella, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - D and R Jones Construction, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Draffen, Duayne, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Drake Bakeries, Inc., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Dresdner, Irwin, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Drekel Burnham Lambert, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Drowne, Irene P (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dukart, Mike (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Duke University (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dullen, Hendrick, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dunietz, Irwin (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dunlop, David R, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Dunn, Christopher P, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dutch Gold Honey, Inc, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dutta, Dean Soumitra, 2013-2015 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Dworkin, David L, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Dyckman, Howard L, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Dyckman, Thomas R, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Eagle Snacks, Inc, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ealahan, William, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Earle, Brian O'Hara, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Earle, Corey, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Eastern Silver Co (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Eastman, Donald, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ecolab, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Eddygate Park Apartments, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Edenbaum, Beth, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Edwards, Rabbi Larry, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Efficiency Systems Co., 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Egan, Shirley K, 1987-1991, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Ehrenberg, Ronald G, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Ehrenberg, A, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - E and I cooperative, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Eisen, Bruce M, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Eisen, Larry and Marsha, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Eisner, Juliana, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Ben-Elissar, Eliahu, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Eissner, Bruce, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Ellison, William, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Queen Elizabeth II, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Elmira Saving and Loan, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Elmira, NY Jewish Community, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Elnaggar, Yasser, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Elwit, Sanford, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Fred Emerson Foundation, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Emerson, Pam, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Emmerich, Andre, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Empire Kosher Foods, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Endlich, Nora, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 49)